elegantcourage.info 2013-12-06

# Privacy Policy

* * *

Cranfield University is committed to the privacy of every individual who visits our website. To that end, the University has established this Privacy Policy to protect each visitor’s privacy. It explains what and how we collect, store, use and protect the information gathered from our websites.

This Policy also instructs you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit our websites.

By using and visiting the website, you agree to this Policy and the uses made of personal information as set forth herein or amended hereafter.

#### Questions

We welcome comments and suggestions regarding the Cranfield University Privacy Policy please send these to our [Data Protection Officer](mailto:dataprotection@cranfield.ac.uk). 

If you believe your personal information has been misused or handled in such a manner contrary to the policy stated above, please [contact the Data Protection Officer](mailto:dataprotection@cranfield.ac.uk).

## [Personal Information]( "Personal Information")

Cranfield University will only collect personal information (information which personally identifies you) if you provide it to us voluntarily. This could include such things as your name, address, phone number or email address. You are in control of how the University uses the information you provide.

At any time you can:

    * ask us to remove your personal information from our records
    * ask for your personal information to be corrected or updated
    * ask to see a copy of your personal information.

We may use your personal information for marketing or research purposes. For instance, this could allow us to personalise information and increase its relevancy if we contact you, or to invite you to help us develop new products through your feedback. If you would prefer us not to contact you using the personal details you have supplied please [contact the Data Protection Officer](mailto:dataprotection@cranfield.ac.uk).

##### Other (non-personal) information collected automatically

Sometimes we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site.

  * 

## Website cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. Cranfield University uses a number of cookies to improve your experience of our website.

More __

## [Security and information transfer]( "Security and information transfer")

Your personally identifiable information will normally be stored in our own databases located in the United Kingdom, but some data may be stored elsewhere either in the European Economic Area, or in the United States under Safe Harbor agreements. Cranfield University is committed to keeping secure the data you provide us and will take reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration.

Cranfield University has made substantial investments in security technology and security management processes. These technologies are deployed to guarantee maximum security of the information you provide us with.

### Email newsletters/communications (electronic communications)

Cranfield University offers visitors to our website the opportunity to subscribe (opt in) to a number of electronic communications. You have the possibility at all times to tell us you no longer wish to subscribe to our electronic communication service (opt out). All e-communications you receive from us will provide clear instructions on how to unsubscribe from each service.

## [Send to a friend]( "Send to a friend")

Users can choose to electronically forward a variety of articles, abstracts, research papers and course details to someone else. Users must provide their email address as well as that of the recipient. The information is used only in the case of transmission errors and to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

## [Changes to our Privacy policy]( "Changes to our Privacy policy")

Cranfield University may change and update this Privacy Policy, including materially changing the use made of personal information described herein. Any change or update to our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website under 'Privacy Policy' at least 30 days prior to its implementation. Your continued use of the website after the effective date of any changes will constitute your acceptance of all of the changes.

## [Limitation/External links]( "Limitation/External links")

This policy is limited to the information that Cranfield University collects from our website users about themselves and others via our websites.  Our sites contain links to other sites. The linkages are provided as a courtesy, to be used or not at the discretion of the individual user. If users decide to follow these links, Cranfield University cannot be responsible for the Privacy Policies and content of those sites. Users should contact the coordinator of the particular site with any questions about those sites.

## [Data Protection Act 1998]( "Data Protection Act 1998")

Please note that any information supplied via this website may be stored on our computer system for the provision of information, marketing and analysis. We may also share this information with other Cranfield University departments for the above purposes. 

Our 1998 Data Protection Act registration number is Z4690919.
